{
  "quizzes": {
    "lesson_1": {
      "title": "Lesson 1: Numbers, Alphabets, Pronunciation & Basic Introduction",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What is '1' in Twi?",
          "options": ["baako", "mmienu", "mmiɛnsa", "ɛnan"],
          "answer": "baako"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is '5' in Twi?",
          "options": ["ɛnan", "anum", "nsia", "nkron"],
          "answer": "anum"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is '10' in Twi?",
          "options": ["edu", "dubaako", "dunson", "dunwɔtwe"],
          "answer": "edu"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is '14' in Twi?",
          "options": ["dumiɛnsa", "dunan", "dunkron", "dunwɔtwe"],
          "answer": "dunan"
        },
        {
          "question": "Do you speak English?",
          "options": ["Woka saa?", "Woka brɔfo kasa?", "Woka aane?", "Meka brɔfo"],
          "answer": "Woka brɔfo kasa?"
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you say 'I love you'?",
          "options": ["Medɔ wo", "Meeba", "Yoo Mati", "Me pε wo"],
          "answer": "Medɔ wo"
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you say 'My name is ...' in Twi?",
          "options": ["Yɛferɛ me ...", "Me din de ...", "Me fri ...", "Sɛn na wɔka ..."],
          "answer": "Me din de ..."
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you say 'I'm from ...' in Twi?",
          "options": ["Me ho yε, me da ase", "Me fri ...", "Aane", "Ebia"],
          "answer": "Me fri ..."
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you say good morning?",
          "options": ["Maakye", "Maaha", "Maadwo", "Mahu"],
          "answer": "Maakye"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is good evening?",
          "options": ["Maakye", "Maaha", "Maadwo", "Mahu"],
          "answer": "Maadwo"
        },
        {
          "question": "Someone comes to greet you in the afternoon, what do they say?",
          "options": ["Maakye", "Maaha", "Maadwo", "Mahu"],
          "answer": "Maaha"
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you reply to 'How are you?' in Twi?",
          "options": ["Me ho yε", "Me ho nyε", "Bɔkɔɔ", "Daabi"],
          "answer": "Me ho yε"
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you say 'Yes' in Twi?",
          "options": ["Aane", "Daabi", "Ebia", "Mennim"],
          "answer": "Aane"
        },
        {
          "question": "How do you say 'I don't know' in Twi?",
          "options": ["Me ho yε", "Mennim", "Aane", "Ebia"],
          "answer": "Mennim"
        }
      ]
    }
  }
}
